glitch.com 2013-09-30

# Privacy Policy | Glitch

Date of Last Revision: May 17, 2011

### Our Policy:

Tiny Speck, Inc. ("Tiny Speck", "we", "us", or "our") provides our website located at www.glitch.com (the "Site"), all Site-related services and products, including the massively multiplayer online game titled "Glitch" and its related services, and all Site-related software (collectively, the Site and such services and software, the "Service"). This Privacy Policy has been created to provide information about our company and the Service to you and sets forth Tiny Speck's policy with respect to information (including personally identifiable data ("Personal Data") and other information) that is collected from visitors to the Site and users of the Service.

### What information do we collect?

When you interact with us through the Service, we may collect Personal Data and other information from you, as further described below:

  * **We collect Personal Data that you provide through the Service:** We collect Personal Data from you when you voluntarily provide such information, such as when you register for access to the Service (for example, username, email address, etc.), use certain components of the Service, contact us with inquiries or respond to one of our surveys. In addition, you may be required to provide us or a third party payment service (e.g., PayPal) with your credit card information (including a valid credit card number, expiration date and shipping and billing addresses) if you wish to purchase items when using the Service. Wherever Tiny Speck collects Personal Data we make an effort to provide a link to this Privacy Policy.
  * **By voluntarily providing us with Personal Data, you are consenting to our use of it in accordance with this Privacy Policy. If you provide Personal Data, you acknowledge and agree that such Personal Data may be transferred from your current location to the offices and servers of Tiny Speck and the authorized third parties referred to herein located in the United States and elsewhere.**
  * **We collect non-identifiable or aggregated data:** When you interact with Tiny Speck through the Service, we receive and store certain personally non-identifiable information (for example, the age range of people who play Glitch). Such information, which is collected passively using various technologies, cannot presently be used to specifically identify you. Tiny Speck may store such information itself or such information may be included in databases owned and maintained by Tiny Speck affiliates, agents or service providers. The Service may use such information and pool it with other information to track, for example, information about the total number of visitors to the Site, the number of users of the Service, the domain names of our visitors' or users' Internet service providers, and how our users use and interact with the Service. Also, in an ongoing effort to better understand and serve the users of the Service, Tiny Speck often conducts research on its customer demographics, interests and behavior based on the Personal Data and other information provided to us. This research may be compiled and analyzed on an aggregate basis.Tiny Speck may share this non-identifiable and aggregate data with its affiliates, agents and business partners, but this type of non-identifiable and aggregate information does not identify you personally. Tiny Speck may also disclose aggregated user statistics in order to describe the Service to current and prospective business partners, and to other third parties for other lawful purposes.
  * **The Service collects other non-identifiable data:** Our Services automatically obtain certain information that is typically required for web-based communication, such as information about your computer or software, your operating system, IP address, and Internet browser, information from your computer's random access memory, video card, central processing unit, hard drive(s) and other storage devices. The scan may detect the use of such programs, including packet editors, cheat engines and WinSocket providers which are in violation of Tiny Speck's Terms of Use. Although such information is not generally personally identifiable, we can determine from an IP address your ISP and the geographic location of your point of connectivity. In order to sign up for any account, you also are required to provide us with a username and password.
  * **Cookies collect data:** In operating the Service, we may also use a technology called "cookies." A cookie is a piece of information that the computer that hosts the Service gives to your browser when you access the Service. Our cookies help provide additional functionality to the Service and help us analyze Service usage more accurately. For instance, the Service may set a cookie on your browser that allows you to access the Service without needing to remember and then enter a password more than once during a visit to the Service. In all cases in which we use cookies, we will not collect Personal Data except with your permission. On most web browsers, you will find a "help" section on the toolbar. Please refer to this section for information on how to receive notification when you are receiving a new cookie and how to turn cookies off. We recommend that you leave cookies turned on because they allow you to take advantage of some of the Service features.

### How do we use your Personal Data and other information?

  * Tiny Speck uses the Personal Data you provide in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy. If you provide Personal Data for a certain reason, we may use the Personal Data in connection with the reason for which it was provided. For instance, if you contact us by email, we will use the Personal Data you provide to answer your question or resolve your problem.
  * If you provide Personal Data in order to obtain access to the Service, we will use your Personal Data to provide you with access to the Service and to monitor your use of the Service.
  * Tiny Speck and its subsidiaries and affiliates, which are companies with which we share ownership (the "Tiny Speck Companies") may also use your Personal Data and other personally non-identifiable information collected through the Service to help us customize the Service or the messages you receive, improve the content and functionality of the Service, to better understand our users and to improve the Service.
  * We may also use this information to communicate with you regarding the Service or to tell you about Tiny Speck related products or services we believe will be of interest to you. If we do so, any marketing communication we send you will contain instructions permitting you to "opt-out" of receiving future marketing communications. In addition, if at any time you wish not to receive any future marketing communications or you wish to have your name deleted from our mailing lists, please contact us as indicated below. Note however that as user of the Service you cannot opt-out of some administrative communications that are reasonably necessary to the Service, such as billing or service notifications.

If Tiny Speck intends on using any Personal Data in any manner that is not consistent with this Privacy Policy, you will be informed of such anticipated use prior to or at the time at which the Personal Data is collected.

### When do we disclose your Personal Data and other information?

Tiny Speck is not in the business of selling your information. We consider this information to be a vital part of our relationship with you. There are, however, certain circumstances in which we may share your Personal Data with certain third parties without further notice to you, as set forth below:

  * **Business Transfers:** As we develop our business, we might sell or buy businesses or assets. In the event of a corporate sale, merger, reorganization, dissolution or similar event, Personal Data may be part of the transferred assets.
  * **Tiny Speck Companies (e.g. our subsidiaries and affiliates):** We may also share your Personal Data with the Tiny Speck Companies for purposes consistent with this Privacy Policy.
  * **Agents, Consultants and Related Third Parties:** Tiny Speck, like many businesses, sometimes hires other companies to perform certain business-related functions. Examples of such functions include mailing information, maintaining databases and processing payments. When we employ another company to perform a function of this nature, we only provide them with the information that they need to perform their specific function.
  * **Legal Requirements:** Tiny Speck may disclose your Personal Data if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to (i) comply with a legal obligation, (ii) protect and defend the rights or property of Tiny Speck, (iii) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of the Service or the public, or (iv) protect against legal liability.

### What are your choices?

  * You can browse the Site without providing any Personal Data. If you choose not to provide any Personal Data, however, you may not be able to use the Service.
  * You may request that we delete your account, and any information associated with your account, but please note that we may be required (by law or otherwise) to retain this information and not delete it (or to keep this information for a certain time, in which case we will comply with your deletion request only after we have fulfilled such requirements). When we delete your information, it will be deleted from the active database but may remain in our archives.

### What doesn't this Privacy Policy cover?

  * This Privacy Policy does not apply to any Personal Data collected by Tiny Speck other than Personal Data collected through the Service.
  * This Privacy Policy will not apply to any unsolicited information you provide to Tiny Speck through the Service or through any other means. This includes, but is not limited to, information posted to any public areas of the Service, such as forums (collectively, "Public Areas"), any ideas for new products or modifications to existing products, and other unsolicited submissions (collectively, "Unsolicited Information"). All Unsolicited Information will be deemed to be non-confidential and Tiny Speck will be free to reproduce, use, disclose, distribute and exploit such Unsolicited Information without limitation or attribution.

### What about children's information?

Tiny Speck does not knowingly collect Personal Data from children under the age of 14. If you are under the age of 14, please do not submit any Personal Data through the Service. We encourage parents and legal guardians to monitor their children's Internet usage and to help enforce our Privacy Policy by instructing their children never to provide Personal Data through the Service without their permission. If you have reason to believe that a child under the age of 14 has provided Personal Data to Tiny Speck through the Service, please contact us, and we will endeavor to delete that information from our databases.

### What if there are links to other websites?

This Privacy Policy applies only to the Service. The Service may contain links to other web sites not operated or controlled by Tiny Speck (the "Third Party Sites"). The policies and procedures we described here do not apply to the Third Party Sites. The links from the Service do not imply that Tiny Speck endorses or has reviewed the Third Party Sites. We suggest contacting those sites directly for information on their privacy policies.

### Integrating Third Party Services within the Service:

One of the special features of the Service is that it allows you to enable various online third party services, include social media and networking services (collectively, "Third Party Services"), to be directly integrated into your Tiny Speck experience. To take advantage of this feature, we may, if necessary, ask you to provide us your username and password for the relevant Third Party Services. By enabling such Third Party Services, you are allowing us to pass your log-in information to these service providers for this purpose (but we will not store this information unless necessary).

When you add a Third Party Service account to the Service, we will collect your login information and other relevant information necessary to enable the Service to access that Third Party Service and your data contained within that Third Party Service. However, please remember that the manner in which Third Party Services use, store and disclose your information is governed solely by the policies of such third parties, and Tiny Speck will have no liability or responsibility for the privacy practices or other actions of any Third Party Service that may be enabled within the Service.

### How does Tiny Speck handle security?

Tiny Speck takes reasonable steps to protect the Personal Data provided via the Service from loss, misuse, and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction. However, no Internet, email or other electronic transmission is ever fully secure or error free, so you should take special care in deciding what information you send to us in this way.

### Other Terms and Conditions:

Your access to and use of the Service is subject to the Terms of Service.

### Changes to Tiny Speck's Privacy Policy:

The Service and our business may change from time to time. As a result, at times it may be necessary for Tiny Speck to make changes to this Privacy Policy. Tiny Speck reserves the right to update or modify this Privacy Policy at any time and from time to time without prior notice. Please review this policy periodically, and especially before you provide any Personal Data. This Privacy Policy was last revised on the date indicated above. Your continued use of the Service after any changes or revisions to this Privacy Policy will indicate your agreement with the terms of such revised Privacy Policy.

### Access to Information; Contacting Tiny Speck:

To keep your Personal Data accurate, current, and complete, please contact us as specified below. We will take reasonable steps to update or correct Personal Data in our possession that you have previously submitted via the Service.

Please also feel free to contact us if you have any questions about Tiny Speck's Privacy Policy or the information practices of Tiny Speck.

You may contact us as follows: [privacy@tinyspeck.com](mailto:privacy@tinyspeck.com).
